ANALIESE QUAMINA

#16 CHIN YUEN KEE TR, CAP-DE-VILLE, POINT FORTIN

Email:laylaq28@hotmail.com

TEL PH: 1868376-9995/468-3836

OBJECTIVE

TO FIND A CHALLENGING CAREER IN AN ESTEEMED ORGANIZATION SO THAT I MAY GROW PROFESSIONALY, WHILST EARNING A GOOD REPUTATION AMONGST MY PEERS. I AM SEEKING A POSITION THAT WILL UTILIZE MY SKILLS AND EXPERTISE WHILST OFFERING THE CHANCES FOR ADVANCEMENT.

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I AM A MOTIVATED INDIVIDUAL OFFERING OVER 10 + YEARS OF COMBINED EXPERIENCE WITHIN THE SERVICE AND HOSPITALITY INDUSTRY, FOCUSED ON HIGH STANDARDS FOR TASTE AND QUALITY, WHILE MAINTAINING PROFITABLE MARGINS .I HAVE EXCELLENT COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS AND I AM WILLING TO CONTINUE MY LEARNING EXPERIENCE WITHIN YOUR HIGHLY RECCOMMENDED ESTABLISHMENT.

SKILLS

- BEAUTIFUL PRESENTATION OF FOOD.
- STRONG ATTENTION TO SAFE FOOD HANDLING PROCEDURES.
- HOSPITALITY AND FOOD SERVICE BACKGROUND.
- SERVICE ORIENTED
- DETAIL ORIENTED
- ADAPTABILITY AND RESPONSIVENESS
- . SELF MOTIVATED
- QUICK LEARNER
- ORGANIZED MULTI-TASKER

WORK HISTORY

1.RECEPTIONIST/CLERICAL ASSISSTANT (PART-TIME)

NOV 2014 TO OCT 2015

EASTMAN GENERAL CONSTRUCTION AND TRANSPORTATION SERVICES, PROFESSIONAL TILING, BOOFING AND FOUNDATION

- Answering telephones.
- Creating timesheets and payslips.
- Paying employees salaries.
- Ordering materials for the company.

2.O.J.T KITCHEN ASSISTANT

SEP 2012 TO SEP 2014

CHATHAM YOUTH DEVELOPMENT AND APPRENTICESHIP CENTRE

Chatham Village, Cedros

- Prepared quality products while maintaining proper food safety practices, portion control and presentation
- within service goal times.

- Assisted in maintaining preparation and service areas in sanitary condition.
- Prepared a variety of foods according to set daily menus or supervisors instructions, following approved procedures.

3.SUPERVISOR/PART-TIME CHEF (CANTEEN) 2011

FEB 2011 TO NOV

NATIONAL ENERGY SKILLS CENTRE

Vessigny Village ,La Brea

- Routinely improved product quality and reduced delivery costs.
- Lead shifts while personally preparing food items and executing requests based on required specifications.
- Assisted in maintaining preparation and service areas in a sanitary condition.
- Purchased stock, took orders and kept stock books for the canteen.

3.FIELD SALES REPRESENTATIVE

MAR 2010 TO NOV 2010

DIREC 1 INTERNATIONAL CALL CENTRE

Independence Square, POS

- Documented all customer/client inquiries and comments quickly and thoroughly.
- Responded to all customer/client inquiries quickly and professionally.
- Greeted each customer/client in a timely fashion, while quickly determining their needs.

4.CHEF/KITCHEN ASSISTANT

'D' ORIGINAL MODERNAIRES KITHCHEN

FEB 2009 TO MAR 2010

Cor. French and Tagarete Rds, Woodbrook, P.O.S.

- Prepared food items consistently and in compliance with recipes, portioning, cooking and waste control
 guidelines.
- Verified proper portion sizes and consistently attained high food quality standards.
- Lead shifts while personally preparing food items and executing requests based on required specifications.

5.GENERAL BAKERY ASSISTANT

OCT 2007 TO FEB 2009

CHERYL'S PASTRY PALACE

Adventure Rd, Point Fortin

- Regularly interacted with guests to obtain feedback on product quality and service levels.
- Inspected kitchens to observe food preparation quality and service, appearance and cleanliness of production and service areas.
- Decorated and merchandised quality bakery goods.
- Properly wrapped, boxed and weighed bakery department goods.

6.M.U.S.T(TRAINEE) CHEF AND FOOD PREPARATION ASSISTANT

JUL 2007 TO SEP 2007

SOUTHWESTERN COURT HOTEL

Main Rd, Point Fortin

- Practiced safe food handling procedures at all times
- Cooked and served food and meals in accordance with planned menus, diet plans, recipes, portions, temperature control procedures and facility policies.
- Properly labeled and stored all raw food ingredients including produce, meat, fish, poultry, dairy and dry goods in the appropriate storage areas.
- Accurately and efficiently prepared healthy, delicious fish, meat and vegetable dishes.

7.WAITRESS AND GENERAL ASSISTANT

RAMDHANSINGH RESTAURANT

Warner Rd, Point Fortin

- Skillfully promoted items on beverages list and restaurant specials.
- Consistently provided professional friendly and engaging service.
- Routinely supported other areas of the restaurant as requested, including answering telephones
 and completing financial transactions for my station as well as others.

EDUCATION

	SUBJECT	PROFICIENCY	GRADE
•	FOOD AND NUTRITION	GENERAL	III (3)
•	SOCIAL STUDIES	GENERAL	II (2)
•	ENGLISH A	GENERAL	II (2)
•	PRINCIPLES OF BUSINESS	GENERAL	II (2)

CERTIFICATION

- CERTIFICATE IN FOOD PREPARATION TTNVQ LEVEL ONE
- CERTIFICATE IN ELECTRICAL INSTALLATION
- CERTIFICATE IN COMPUTER LITERACY

REFERENCES

1. CPL.CARLOS MORALES #15960

TRINIDAD AND TOBAGO POLICE SERVICE

ERIN POLICE STATION

BEACH RD,

ST FRANCIS VILLAGE ERIN

PH #: (WORK) 649-8888

: (CELL) 327-8483

2. MR.JEFFREY HOLDER

CAMP DIRECTOR 1

CHATHAM YOUTH DEVELOPMENT AND APPRENTICESHIP CENTRE

#2430 SOUTHERN MAIN RD, CHATHAM VILLAGE, CEDROS

PH # 648-2397/56

3. MR KIRT CHARLES

ASSISTANT DIRECTOR

CHATHAM YOUTH DEVELOPMENT AND APPRENTICESHIP CENTRE

#2430 SOUTHERN MAIN RD, CHATHAM VILLAGE CEDROS

PH # 387-2287